(party guests chattering)
♪ This is how we do it ♪
(upbeat R&B music)
♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ It's Friday night
and I feel all right ♪
♪ The party is here
on the west side ♪
♪ So I reach for my
40 and I turn it up ♪
♪ Designated driver take
the keys to my truck ♪
♪ Hit the shore
'cause I'm faded ♪
♪ Honies in the street
say, Monty, yo we made it ♪
♪ It feels so good
in my hood tonight ♪
♪ The summertime skirts
and my guys in Kani ♪
♪ All the gangbangers
forgot about the drive-by ♪
♪ You gotta get your groove
on before you go get paid ♪
♪ So tip up your cup and
throw your hands up ♪
♪ And let me hear
the party say ♪
♪ I'm kinda buzzed
and it's all because ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ South Central does
it like nobody does ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ To all my neighbors,
you got much flavor ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Let's flip the track,
bring the old school back ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ This is how we do it,
all hands are in the air ♪
♪ And wave them
from here to there ♪
♪ If you're an OG mack
or a wannabe player ♪
♪ You see the hood's
been good to me ♪
♪ Ever since I was
a lowercase g ♪
♪ But now I'm a big G ♪
♪ The girls see
I got the money ♪
♪ Hundred dollar bills, y'all ♪
♪ If you were from where I'm
from, then you would know ♪
♪ That I gotta get mine
in a big black truck ♪
♪ You can get yours in a '64 ♪
♪ Whatever it is, the
party's underway ♪
♪ So tip up your cup and
throw your hands up ♪
♪ And let me hear
the party say ♪
♪ I'm kinda buzzed,
it's all because ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Oh, South Central does
it like nobody does ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ To all my neighbors,
you got much flavor ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Let's flip the track,
bring the old school back ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ I'm kinda buzzed,
it's all because ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ South Central does
it like nobody does ♪
♪ This is how we do it
nobody does ♪
♪ YNV, SCC ♪
♪ This is how we do it
All my homies ♪
♪ I'll never come wack
on an old school track ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Check it out ♪
♪ Once upon a time in '94 ♪
♪ Montell made no money
and life sure was slow ♪
♪ And all they said
was 6'8" he stood ♪
♪ And people thought the
music that he made was good ♪
♪ There lived a DJ and
Paul was his name ♪
♪ He came up to Monty,
this is what he said ♪
♪ You and OG are
gonna make some cash ♪
♪ Sell a million records
and we're making the dash ♪
♪ Oh, I'm buzzing because ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ South Central does
it like nobody does ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ To all my neighbors,
you got much flavor ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ I'll never come wack
on an old school track ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ I'm kinda buzzed,
it's all because ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ South Central does
it like nobody does ♪
♪ This is how we do it
nobody does ♪
♪ Oh, it's party time ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Straight up coming
from the west side ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Oh, she's got
the flavor, yeah ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ And Monty does it
like nobody does ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Come on now, Def Jam ♪
♪ You know that this
is how we do it ♪
♪ This is how we do it ♪